AAKASH GUPTA



behance.net/aakashgupta7

linkedin.com/in/aakash-gupta-699b25164/



EXPERIENCE

User Experience Designer @ Tericsoft Technology Solutions Pvt. Ltd.

October 2021- February 2022

I worked here as UX Designer, It was a fantastic experience working on Live Projects assigned from USA. I worked on some of the Websites and Mobile application and Improve their Usability and user experience by collaborating with Tech Team.

UI/UX Designer @ AICTE

July 2020 - January 2021

There was a great working experience with aicte (All India Council for technical Education), I have learned about the team work and designed some web portals, SOP's etc for NHAI and Ministry of railways.

ABOUT ME

I am an enthusiastic UX/UI Designer with problem solving skills and learning experience in wireframing, Information architecture, prototyping and making the better user experiences. Along with Technical Skills of design tools like adobe XD, Figma, photoshop, I have Soft skills like Empathy, Communication and Curiosity to learn something new.

CONTACT DETAILS

- +91 8708779129
- aakashgupta17697@gmail.com
- Ambala Cantt, India

SKILLS

- Adobe XD
- Figma
- Adobe Photoshop
- Invision
- MS Word, Powerpoint

Live Project on Careersetkaro website

June 2021

There was a great learning experience working on a live project. It was a group project of 8 people and each of us has done our part with all the energies using the best of our skills, Basically it was a redesigning of whole experience of careersetkaro website.

UX SKILLS

User Research, Brainstorming, Wireframing, User Flows, Information architecture and Prototyping.

INTERESTS

Cricket, Traveling, Gaming, Music

LANGUAGES

English, Hindi

EDUCATION

Masters in UX/UI

Chitkara University, Punjab

Bachelors of computers & applications

Institute of Management & studies, Noida, UP

2015-2018

2019-Present

CERTIFICATES

Digital Skills: User Experience by Accenture



